uitvconnect.com 2014-04-07

# Privacy |Welcome to UITV Internet Television, High Definition Internet Television, Online Movie Trailers, Live Telecast Matches, Music, Entertainment, Lifestyle Videos, Online Movies

### UITV Privacy Policy

The UITV Privacy Policy describes how UITV and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use UITV services, including information provided when you use UITV.

In addition, the following describes privacy practices specific to UITV. Personal Information Browsing UiTV You can watch videos on UiTV without having a UiTV Account. You can also contact us through the UiTV Help Centre or by emailing us at [marketing@uitvconnect.com ](http://mailto:marketing@uitvconnect.com/) directly, without having to register for an account.

Your UiTV Account. For some activities on UiTV, such as uploading videos, posting comments, flagging videos or watching restricted videos, you need a UiTV Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorised access. Usage Information.

When you use UiTV, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the channels, groups and favourites to which you subscribe, which other users you communicate with, the videos that you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers and information that you display about yourself, as well as information that you click in UiTV (including UI elements, settings).

If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your UiTV Account. In order to ensure the quality of our service to you, we may place a tag (also called a "web beacon") in HTML-based customer support emails or other communications with you in order to confirm delivery. Content Uploaded to Site.

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g. video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others.

If you download the UiTV Uploader, your copy includes a unique application number. This number and information about your installation of the Uploader (version number, language) will be sent to UiTV when the Uploader automatically checks for updates and will be used to update your version of the Uploader.

**Uses**

If you submit personal information to UiTV, we may use that information to operate, maintain and improve the features and functionality of UiTV, and to process any flagging activity or other communication that you send to us.

We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.

We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major UiTV changes or for customer service purposes).

You can also choose how often UiTV sends you email updates in your UiTV Account settings page.

**Information**

That is Publicly Available When you create a UiTV Account, some information about your UiTV Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of UiTV. This may include the date that you opened your UiTV Account, the date that you last logged in to your UiTV Account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of videos that you have watched.

Your UiTV Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on UiTV, such as when you upload videos or send messages through UiTV.

Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.

Any videos that you submit to UiTV may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels and may be viewed by other UiTV users or the general public.

You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your UiTV Account channel page. If you choose to add certain features to your UiTV Account channel page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other users and may be aggregated and shared with your friends or other users. Such shared activity may include your favourite videos, videos that you rated and videos that you have uploaded.

**Your Choices**

If you have a UiTV Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information, email preferences and privacy settings at any time by visiting your UiTV account profile page.

You may control the information that is available to other users and your confirmed friends at any time by editing your UiTV Account and the features that are included on your channel page.

You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through UITV, in which case you can still view videos and explore UITV, but UITV may not be able to provide certain services to you.

Some advanced UITV features may use other services such as Paypal or AdSense. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

Advertising on UITV UITV strives to provide you with relevant and useful advertising and we use third-party ad-serving systems. We may use a range of information, including cookies, web beacons, IP addresses, usage data and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as browser type and operating system) to provide you with relevant advertising.

If you are logged in to your UITV Account, we may also show you advertising based on the information that you have provided to us in your UITV Account. We use cookies on UITV to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads on this site and other partner websites.

Advertisers may serve ads based on interests associated with non-personally identifiable online activity, such as videos viewed, frequency of uploading or activity on other partner sites.

Advertisers may also serve ads to you based on previous activity on that advertiser's website. This non-personally identifiable information is held separately from your UITV Account data or other personally identifying information in our possession. You may also choose to opt out of the cookies at any time.

**Cookies**

The UiTV Connect website (the "Website") uses cookies to deliver a better and more personalised service to users.  

This Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how they are used on the Website and how to manage their use.  

What is a Cookie?  
Cookies are small text files containing small amounts of information which are sent to and stored on your computer, smartphone or other device when you access a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user's device.  

You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). A video about cookies can be found at [www.google.co.uk/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies](http://www.google.co.uk/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies).  

Use of Cookies on the Website  
Cookies are used on the Website for a number of reasons. This includes, but is not limited to, the following:

  * to allow users to log on to their UiTV Connect account;
  * to allow users to choose log-in preferences;
  * to monitor and collect information about transactions placed on the Website; and
  * for fraud prevention purposes and to generally safeguard privacy.

Cookies are generally used to improve and enhance the user experience. Some of the cookies we use are essential for the Website to operate.  

UiTV Connect’s use of cookies on the Website falls into the following categories:  

**Session Management** \- these cookies are essential to enable use of the Website, they manage session information and enable users to navigate through the Website.  

**Functionality** \- these cookies store information which enables us to remember user preferences e.g. preferred language, sort types, media settings. They are also used to improve user's experience by, for example, stopping users from being shown the same message twice.  

**Fraud Prevention** \- these cookies store information which help us stop fraudulent use of the Website.  

**Tracking** \- these cookies enable us to store information about how users landed on the Website. We need to record this so that we can appropriately pay our Affiliates.  

Where links are provided on the Website to third party websites it is important to remember that those websites will have their own cookies and privacy policies which will govern any information you may submit. If you decide to use any linked third party websites please read their cookies and privacy policies before doing so.  

Managing Cookies  
If you want to delete any cookies already stored on your computer or stop the cookies that keep track of your browsing patterns on the Website you can do so by deleting your existing cookies and/or altering your browser's privacy settings (the process you follow will differ from browser to browser). If you would like more information on how to disable cookies or change your privacy settings please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Your browser's 'help' function should also tell you how to do this.  

Please note that deleting our cookies or disabling our future cookies means that you may not be able to access certain areas or features of the Website. For example, if your browser is set to disable 'session' cookies you won't be able to log on to your UiTV Connect account.  

Other third-party ad-serving companies may display ads on UITV, provided that they comply with our ad-serving requirements. UITV does not provide any personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt out of certain practices.

UITV privacy policy does not apply to and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with UITV are maintained and dealt with by UITV in accordance with this privacy policy. More Information For questions concerning the product or your account, please contact us at [marketing@uitvconnect.com ](http://mailto:marketing@uitvconnect.com/)

For more information about our privacy practices, write to us at: please send to [marketing@uitvconnect.com ](http://mailto:marketing@uitvconnect.com/)
